[
  {
	"id": "tucker",
	"name": "Tucker",
  	"tagline": "The Brother",
	"status": "Confirmed - 3rd (potentially DQ'ed for cheating)",
	"questions": [
	  {
		"question": "After watching many hours of 101 Dalmatians, I developed this nickname for you.",
		"answer": "nodie"
	  },
	  {
		"question": "Name my most recent Hanukkah gift to you, in order. (comma-separated, no spaces)",
		"answer": "nidoking,clefable,dugtrio,victreebel,gyarados,ditto,moltres"
	  },
	  {
		"question": "Your code:",
		"answer": "moopin8r"
	  }
	],
	"ask": "Since you were born you've been my best friend. From playing video games of every genre, to skiing and snowboarding, to playing soccer as the last two defenders, we've done it all together. You always push me to the edge mentally and physically and even though that drives me crazy sometimes, I love it. On my most carefree days, I still think about pulling up a chair right next to you and grinding through as much Gears of War as possible before we have to do chores. I'm thankful we grew up so close in age to share so many things together and I know I'll want the same for my children in the future. I know having one of me is tough, and Rachel and I are very much alike, so I've always loved how you've treated her kindly and with open arms to the family. I couldn't imagine having a better man by my side the day I marry Rachel. Tucker, will you be my best man?"
  },
  {
	"id": "jake",
	"name": "Jake",
	"tagline": "Yaakov",

	"status": "Awaiting Confirmation","questions": [
	  {
		"question": "I was placed in a different cabin than my two best friends at this overnight camp.",
		"answer": "timber ridge"
	  },
	  {
		"question": "The party of the millennium was almost ruined from a fight between us stemming from this game.",
		"answer": "pokemon"
	  },
	  {
		"question": "Your code:",
		"answer": "pinkranger"
	  }
	],
	"ask": "It's crazy to realize that I've known you longer than my own brother. Although I can't remember our exact first memories together, some of the earliest memories of my life have you in them. From reading books together in pre-school at the JCC to me actually bringing you in for show-and-tell the following year in Kindergartern, you truly were my very first friend. I'm so glad to have kept that through all these years. That kind of friendship is not only rare throughout all of time, but especially in today's world. From hundreds of soccer matches together, to a few tennis matches against each other, we've done so much together. Even though you'll trade away rare pokemon cards for common ones, you'll always be my best friend. Jake, will you be my groomsman?"
  },
  {
	"id": "jordan",
	"name": "Jordan",
	"tagline": "The Kocenator",
	"status":  "Awaiting Confirmation",
	"questions": [
	  {
		"question": "Although it may not appear on an \"official\" transcript, this was the one class we shared in high school. You even have half of a t-shirt to prove it.",
		"answer": "math modeling"
	  },
	  {
		"question": "As \"Pepe\" once witnessed, Sam took you down in FIFA using this popular Spanish player (last name).",
		"answer": "torres"
	  },
	  {
		"question": "Your code:",
		"answer": "hugo"
	  }
	],
	"ask": "It's crazy to realize that I've known you longer than my own brother. Although it's hard to remember our earliest memories together, I will always remember my favorite ones. From playing manhunt and airsoft in your neighborhood, to tennis camps, to wearing your number during Godwin football games, we've done a lot together. You truly were my very first friend. I'm so glad to have kept that through all these years. That kind of friendship is not only rare throughout all of time, but especially in today's world. You've always been my \"cool\" friend and would never shy away from hanging out with the nerds. Even when you're traveling the world with thousands of other people, I know we'll always be best friends. Jordan, will you be my groomsman?"
  },
  {
	"id": "tj",
	"name": "TJ",
	"tagline": "The Doctor",
	"status":  "Awaiting Confirmation",
	"questions": [
	  {
		"question": "When writing our national outstanding math modeling paper, a certain member of our team became fixated on this.",
		"answer": "regions"
	  },
	  {
		"question": "This political TV show was acted out poorly during a game of Catch Phrase with Tucker and his friend.",
		"answer": "west wing"
	  },
	  {
		"question": "Your code:",
		"answer": "snorlax"
	  }
	],
	"ask": "When my family moved to Fox Hall before 5th grade, I had no idea I'd be making a new best friend. I can't recall exactly how we first became friends, but I have to imagine you walked over, rang the doorbell, and we simply proceeded to play some videogames, shoot some hoops, and crush some snacks from my pantry. From there, the rest is history. It seems like time flew through high school and college- playing Spades together in class, playing soccer as co-defenders, watching U.Va basketball games (back when Jeff Jones was there), hanging out at Ocean City, taking our Senior trip cruise, living together two years at U.Va- we've done so much together. I'm glad to have shared those and many more memories with you throughout the years. That kind of friendship is not only rare throughout all of time, but especially in today's world. Aside from your sports statistics, you're probably one of the most honest and down-to-earth friends that I have and I've always appreciated that about you. You hold the special honor of being the first of the bunch to have met my future wife. Even though you've already graciously accepted to be our officiant, TJ, will you be my groomsman?"
  },
  {
	"id": "matt",
	"name": "Matt",
	"tagline": "Bag",
	"status":  "Awaiting Confirmation",
	"questions": [
	  {
		"question": "We're in Spain. Barcelona, specifically. Actually, doesn't matter where we are. What does matter is that it is 3am and we are having a blast and your flight leaves at 6am. Its a one hour drive to the airport. You don't want to leave. I ask you this question.",
		"answer": "what would kochard do"
	  },
	  {
		"question": "You have health and long life, land without rent, and a child every year. You're not in Ireland. But you are playing blackjack and are dealt cards that remind you of us. Dealer shows a 19. You bet $85. You leave the table with this much in your pocket.",
		"answer": "128"
	  },
	  {
		"question": "Your code:",
		"answer": "floaton"
	  }
	],
	"ask": "It's crazy to think that we've been friends for nearly 15 years, more than half of my life. It seems like time flew through high school and college- playing Spades together in class, playing soccer together, hanging out at Ocean City, taking our Senior trip cruise, pledging together, Europe trip, and living together for four years- we've done so much together. I'm glad to have shared those and many more memories with you throughout the years. That kind of friendship is not only rare throughout all of time, but especially in today's world. You're one of my most reliable friends and I always know if there's one person I can count on for anything- it's you. You're obviously one of the few friends I have that is very close to both Rachel and me, and we've loved sharing so many fun memories with you. Even though you might \"shake your damn head\" at me while I antagonize Billy and others, I know that we'll always be best friends. Matt, will you be my groomsman?"
  },
  {
	"id": "arjun",
	"name": "Arjun",
	"tagline": "AJ from LSU",
	"status":  "Confirmed - 1st",
	"questions": [
	  {
		"question": "In Senora Andueza's Spanish class, Jonathan B. and crew shouted this pun, referencing a popular video game series.",
		"answer": "Call of Booty"
	  },
	  {
		"question": "Per TJ's 2018 recorded statistical analysis, this person is the best sharp shooter in 21 cup, out-shooting even you.",
		"answer": "sam"
	  },
	  {
		"question": "Your code:",
		"answer": "arthunth"
	  }
	],
	"ask": "It's crazy to think the first time I met you, you were just some dude folding dodecahedrons in our advanced math class. Little did I know, however, that you were the coolest nerd I'll have ever met. It seems like time flew through middle school and beyond- playing SoF together in class, playing soccer together, hanging out at Ocean City, taking our Senior trip cruise, man week trips- we've done so much together. I'm glad to have shared those and many more memories with you throughout the years. That kind of friendship is not only rare throughout all of time, but especially in today's world. Of all my friends, you always have the ability to make me laugh when situations get too serious and are one of the few people I know who can talk to anyone no matter what mood they're in. Even if we're cities apart, I know we will always be friends and I always look forward to when we're together. Arjun, will you be my groomsman?"
  },
  {
	"id": "ajay",
	"name": "Ajay",
	"tagline": "The Kobe",
	"status":  "Confirmed - 2nd",
	"questions": [
	  {
		"question": "Your dedication to the [same] team inspired me to buy my first NBA jersey, representing this big man (nickname)",
		"answer": "shaq"
	  },
	  {
		"question": "This middle school won the Henrico County Tennis Championship.",
		"answer": "moody"
	  },
	  {
		"question": "Your code:",
		"answer": "longchipotle"
	  }
	],
	"ask": "It's crazy to think that of all of the \"center\" friends, I've known you the longest. I can still remember back in the elementary school days where we'd get home and play basketball, football, and ride bikes together in the neighborhood. After that, it seems like time flew through high school, college, and beyond- playing years of soccer together, hanging out at Ocean City, U.Va basketball games, man week trips- we've done so much together. I'm glad to have shared those and many more memories with you throughout the years. That kind of friendship is not only rare throughout all of time, but especially in today's world. Of all my friends, you are the kindest and one of the most down-to-earth. Even if we're cities apart, I know we will always be friends and I always look forward to when we're together. Ajay, will you be my groomsman?"
  },
  {
	"id": "michael",
	"name": "Michael",
	"tagline": "Wolfpack of One",
	"status":  "Awaiting Confirmation",
	"questions": [
	  {
		"question": "After telling you one of the greatest lies I've ever told to win a game. You, as a true friend, warned me, that this competitor would be targeting me at a soccer match.",
		"answer": "ben terner"
	  },
	  {
		"question": "As the first of the \"Wyndham\" bunch that I met, we shared this science teacher at our new school (last name).",
		"answer": "leith"
	  },
	  {
		"question": "Your code:",
		"answer": "gohoos"
	  }
	],
	"ask": "It's crazy to think that we've known each other for more than 15 years now, dating back to our elementary school days. It seems like time flew through elementary school and beyond- taking trips out to Ocean City, many games of 21 cup, taking our Senior trip cruise, man week trips- we've done so much together. I'm glad to have shared those and many more memories with you throughout the years. That kind of friendship is not only rare throughout all of time, but especially in today's world. Of all my friends, you are one of the few who never hesitates to call me, or others, out on BS and I've always appreciated that about you. Even if we're cities apart, I know we will always be friends and I always look forward to when we're together. Michael, will you be my groomsman?"
  }
]
